John Martin Gasangue Software Developer



johnmartingasangue.netlify.app jmgasangue@gmail.com +63 968 638 4987 0599 Phase 3 Saturn street Ecotrend Subdivision, San Nicolas 1, Bacoor City, Cavite

About Me

An IT graduate who's specialized in software development with knowledge in web development and is proficient in programming languages such as C++, C#, and Java.

Relevant Skills

- Programming Languages: C++, C#, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Programming Tools: Microsoft Visual Studio, Android Studio

Work Experience



IT Support

Cultural Center of the Philippines
August 2022 to December 2022 (5 months)



President

Junior Philippine Computer Society - SDCA Chapter August 2021 to August 2022 (1 year)



Auditor

Junior Philippine Computer Society - SDCA Chapter August 2019 to May 2020 (1 year)

Projects



Home Service Provider App

Capstone Project

- Programming Language: Java
- Operating System: Android
- Software Development: Android Studio
- Design Tool: Canva



My Portfolio Website

Portfolio Website

- Programming Language: JavaScript
- Framework: Nextjs, Tailwind CSS
- Website Development: Visual Studio Code
- Design Tool: Canva

Education History



Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

St. Dominic College of Asia *Year of Graduation: 2023*

- Campus Leadership Award: Student Leaders Council 2023
- Dean's Lister: Second Semester A.Y. 2021-2022
- Dean's Lister: First Semester A.Y. 2021-2022



Information and Communications Technology (Senior High School)

Arellano University - Apolinario Mabini Campus

Year of Graduation: 2018



Junior High School

Arellano University - Apolinario Mabini Campus

Year of Graduation: 2018

Certificates

Test of English for International Communication 2023

April 18, 2023

Cultural Center of the Philippines: Internship Program at the Management Services Division

December 13, 2022

18th Cinemalaya Philippine Independent Film Festival 2022

August 19, 2022

Test of English for International Communication 2022

February 18, 2022

JavaScript Essential Training (2017)

December 13, 2021

CSS Essential Training

November 2, 2021

HTML Essential Training

September 28, 2021

Microsoft Office Specialist: Office PowerPoint 2016

March 29, 2019

Microsoft Office Specialist: Office Word 2016

November 20, 2018